<html>
  <head>
    <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">Посол России посетил Белиз </se>
    <se lang="es" variant_id="1">Russian Ambassador Visits Belize </se>
  </head>
  <date>
    <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">24 сентября / 2021</se>
    <se lang="es" variant_id="1">24 de septiembre / 2021</se>
  </date>
  <source>
    <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">https://mexico.mid.ru/ru/novosti/posol_rossii_posetil_beliz/</se>
    <se lang="es" variant_id="1">https://mexico.mid.ru/es/noticias/russian_ambassador_visits_belize/</se>
  </source>
  <country>Mexico</country>
  <body>
    <para id="0">
      <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">17–24 сентября 2021 года Чрезвычайный и Полномочный Посол Российской Федерации в Мексике и в Белизе по совместительству В.В.Коронелли посетил Белиз по приглашению Министра иностранных дел, внешней торговли и иммиграции этой страны И.Кортни для участия в торжественных мероприятиях, посвященных празднованию 40-й годовщины независимости центральноамериканского государства.</se>
      <se lang="es" variant_id="1">On September 17–24, 2021, Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary of the Russian Federation to Belize with Residence in Mexico, Viktor Koronelli, visited Belize at the invitation of the Minister of Foreign Affairs, Foreign Trade and Immigration, Eamon Harrison Courtenay, to take part in the celebrations of the 40th anniversary of the country’s independence.</se>
    </para>
    <para id="1">
      <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">Посол принял участие в обширной программе, включавшей в себя, помимо протокольных праздничных мероприятий, брифинги Генерал-губернатора Белиза Ф.Тзалам, главы МИД И.Кортни, первого заместителя Министра финансов К.Коя и лидера оппозиции П.Фабера, а также ланч представителей аккредитованного в стране дипломатического корпуса с Премьер-министром Дж.Брисеньо.</se>
      <se lang="es" variant_id="1">The Russian Ambassador participated in a wide official programme that, in addition to the celebration ceremonies, included briefings by the Governor General, Froyla Tzalam, Foreign Minister, Eamon Courtenay, Minister of State in the Ministry of Finance, Christopher Coye, and the Leader of Opposition, Patrick Faber, as well as the Prime Minister John Briceño’s lunch with the diplomatic corps.</se>
    </para>
    <para id="2">
      <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">18 сентября В.В.Коронелли провел встречу с мининдел Белиза И.Кортни, в ходе которой обсуждался широкий круг вопросов двусторонней повестки дня.</se>
      <se lang="es" variant_id="1">On September 18, Ambassador Koronelli held a meeting with the Minister of Foreign Affairs, Foreign Trade and Immigration of Belize, Eamon Harrison Courtenay, to discuss a wide range of topics of the bilateral agenda.</se>
    </para>
    <para id="3">
      <se lang="ru" variant_id="0">Собеседнику передано послание Министра иностранных дел Российской Федерации С.В.Лаврова с поздравлениями по случаю 40-летия независимости Белиза.</se>
      <se lang="es" variant_id="1">He handed to Minister Courtenay a message by the Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Russian Federation, Sergey Lavrov, with congratulations on the 40th anniversary of the independence of Belize.</se>
    </para>
  </body>
</html>